mynation.com 2019-09-21

# Privacy Policy | MyNation

The Company recognises the importance of maintaining the privacy of the information belonging to you. This Policy sets out details of how we treat user information we collect on all domain/subdomains related to mynation.comm (the "Website"). The Website is owned and operated by Asianet News Media and Entertainment Private Limited, a private limited company registered under the provisions of the [Indian] Companies Act 2013 having its registered office at No. 36, Crescent Road, Bangalore 560 001, Karnataka, India (the “Company”).

By visiting and/or using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and it shall be deemed that you have read in full, accepted and agreed to the terms herein. The Company reserves the right to modify the terms contained in this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such modifications on the Website. The modified Privacy Policy would be effective from the date of modification that is posted by the Company on the Website. If you do not agree to any term that is contained in this Privacy Policy, please immediately cease your use of the Website.

This Privacy Policy is issued pursuant to the provisions that are contained in (a) Section 43A of the Information Technology Act, 2000; (b) Regulation 4 of the Information Technology ((Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011; and (c) Regulation 3(1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011. 

Information that is collected by the Company on the Website shall be used by the Company only for the purpose of providing the news and entertainment related content and information on the Website (the “Content”), and such information shall not be used, sold, transferred or rented in a manner that is not set out in this Privacy Policy. 

## Information that is collected by the Company:

In making available the Content on the Website, the Company may have to collect certain personal information from you. This information would, inter alia, include the following: 

**Contact information:** the Company may collect your name, email, mobile number, postal address, IP address etc. 

**Other information.** While you use the Website, the Company may collect information about your geographical location, IP address, browser type, operating system, referral source, length of visit and nature of the Content viewed, Website navigation, pixel tag etc. 

You acknowledge and agree that any and all information that is provided by you on the Website is provided by you voluntarily and at your own risk. While the Company would make all efforts to ensure the safety and security of the information provided for you, it shall not be responsible for any loss or theft of data. Please note that any information that is provided by you may be retained by the Company for (i) providing the access to the Content in a manner that is preferred by you; and (ii) for meeting its obligations under applicable law. [Even if you delete your User account on Website, the Company may have to retain the information provided by you for a short period of time until the same can be removed from its servers, and for compliance with its obligations under law (if any).] 

You shall be responsible for the accuracy of the information provided to the Company for the use of the Website. If there is any mistake in or change to the personal information provided by you for the use of Website, you shall immediately notify the Company at feedback@mynation.com. You shall be solely liable for the consequences of providing incomplete, inaccurate or incorrect information on the Website. Where the Company has reasons to believe that the information provided by you on the Website in incorrect or incomplete, the Company may restrict you from using the Website by disabling your User Account. 

If you want to discontinue the use of the Website, or if you want to withdraw the consent granted to the Website for collecting and processing your data, please notify the Company at feedback@mynation.com. Once you discontinue the use of the Website or withdraw your consent, the Company shall retain the personal information provided by you on the Website for such time period as may be mandated by applicable law and thereafter erase the same in full.

## Information may be collected in several ways:

**Active collection:** This refers to the information that is actively provided by you while browsing the Website, while sharing Content (by using the share button on the Website) to social media platforms or making comments on the Website etc. 

**Passive Collection:** This refers to the information that is gathered by the Company using tracking tools like Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, browser cookies etc. for collecting information about your usage of our website. This information may be used by the Company for internal research to understand User demographics, interests and behaviour with a view to improving the functionality of the Website. This information may include the URL of the website that you visited just before visiting the Website or which one you go to after visiting the Website, your computer browser information, and your IP address.

## Use of your personal information by the Company:

**To improve the quality of the Content.** The Company might use your information to improve the functionality of the Website and the Content as well as the manner in which it is presented. 

**For marketing purposes.** The Company might send you information about new Content on the Website or notify you of new or improved features on the Website. 

The Company shall use your information only in a manner that is permitted by applicable law. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

## Sharing of information by the Company with third-parties:

**Compliance with law.** The Company might share your information to respond to a court order or subpoena. The Company may share your information if a government agency or investigatory body requests the Company to do so.

**Mergers and Acquisitions.** If the Company sells its business or hives of a portion of the same to a new entity, your personal information that is available on the Website may be transferred to the new entity.

## SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

Please note that neither the Company nor any of its employees would have access to the password that relates to your User account on the Website. You shall be solely responsible for protecting your login credentials to the Website, and the Company shall not be liable in any manner for unauthorised use of your login credentials. You shall be liable to the Company for any loss suffered by the Company as a result of unauthorised use of your login credentials. In the event of any misuse or suspected misuse of the same, please notify the Company at feedback@mynation.com

While the Company shall seek to implement the best market practices and security policies for the protection of your personal information, it shall not be liable for improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. It is expressly stated that the Company shall not be responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive Users' personal data or events that are beyond the reasonable control of the Company including, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorized access to computer data and storage devices and storage technology, hardware, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption etc.

Cookies: A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you grant the permission, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. The Company uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps the Company analyze data about web page traffic and improve the functioning of the Website. This information is used by the Company only for statistical analysis and then the data is removed from the system. Please note that the Company does not have any control over the cookies that are placed by third party links on the Website. The Company does not represent to you that such third party websites have their own Privacy Policies or that the information that is provided by you to them would be secure. 

## THIRD PARTY SITES 

If you click on one of the links to third party websites that may be available on the Website, you may be taken to websites that the Company does not control. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. 

The Company shall not be liable for the misuse of your personal information by third party websites. 

The Company may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when a User visits the Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

## REDRESSAL OF GRIEVANCES

If a User has any questions or grievances regarding the Website, the contents thereof, the manner in which personal data is being collated or processed by the Website or regarding the Services, the User may reach out to the designated Grievance Officer of the Company at feedback@mynation.com (the “Grievance Officer”). The Grievance Officer shall address any complaint or grievance that is raised by a User within a period of one (1) month from when it is raised. 

Where the Company requires additional information to process and respond to the query raised by a User, the Company shall notify the User of the same. 

## MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS 

Force Majeure. The Company shall not be responsible for any cessation, interruption or delay in the performance of its obligations hereunder due to earthquake, flood, fire, storm, natural disaster, act of God, war, terrorism, armed conflict, labor strike, lockout, or boycott. The Company may at any time, in its sole discretion and without advance notice to you, cease operation of the Website and the provision of the Services.

No Waiver. A delay or failure by the Company to exercise or enforce any right or provision of this Privacy Policy will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. 

Notices: All notices given to a User by the Company or by a User to the Company or another User shall be in writing and in the English language. Such notice shall be sent by e-mail or mailed by a prepaid internationally-recognized courier service to the intended recipient at the address set out below, or any changed address that is notified by either Party: Notice to the Company:  
Asianet News Media and Entertainment Private Limited  
No. 36, Crescent Road, Bangalore 560 001  
Email: feedback@mynation.com  
Notice to User:  
At the email address provided by you at the time of registration on the Website.

Governing Law; Jurisdiction. This Privacy Policy is governed by the provisions of Indian law, including but not limited to the following:

  1. The Indian Contract Act, 1872;
  2. The (Indian) Information Technology Act, 2000; 
  3. The (Indian) Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011; and 
  4. The (Indian) Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011. 

This Website originates from the State of Karnataka in India. This Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws that are applicable in the State of Karnataka. By using this Website, you consent to the jurisdiction and venue of the courts located in Karnataka, India in connection with any action, suit, proceeding or claim arising under or by reason of this Privacy Policy.
